let quiz   =[
    {question: "To draw a pair of tangents to a circle which are inclined to each other at an angle of 60 degree, it is required to draw tangents at end points of those two radii of the circle, the angle between them should be",
option:[
    "135 degree",
    "90 degree",
    "60 degree",
    "120 degree",

],
answer:4, 
},

{
    question: "The Tops of two poles of height 20 m and 14 m are connected by a wire. If the wire makes an angle of 30 degree with horizontal, the length of the wire is " ,
option:[
    "6 m",
    "10 m",
    "12 m",
    "20 m",


],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "The largest number that will divide 398,436 and 542 leaving remainders 7,11 and 15 respectively is",
option:[
    17,
    11,
    34,
    45,


],
answer:1, 
},
{question: "The shadow of a tower is equal to its height at 10:45 A.M . The sun's altitude is ",
option:[
    "30 degree",
    "60 degree",
    "45 degree",
    "90 degree",

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "The product of a rational and irrational number is",
option:[
    "Rational",
    "Irational",
    "Both Rational and Irational",
    "None of these",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "The sum of a rational and irrational number is",
option:[
    "Irational",
    "Rational",
    "Both Rational and Irational",
    "None of these",

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "The area of a circle is 2464 sq. cm , then its diameter is given by ",
option:[
    "51 cm",
    "50 cm",
    "52 cm",
    "56 cm",

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "If In triangle ABC, <c=90 degree, then Sin (A+B) " ,
option:[
    0,
    "1/2",
    "Infinify",
    1,


],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "If Cos 9A = Sin A and 9A < 90 degree ,then the value of Tan 5A is",
option:[
    0,
    1,
    "Infinify",
    "Not Defined",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "If the sum of three numbers in an A.P. is 9 and their product is 24,then numbers are ",
option:[
    "2,3,4",
    "1,5,3",
    "2,8,4",
    "2,4,6",

    
],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "If p,q,r and s are in A.P then r-q is",
option:[
    "s-p",
    "s-q",
    "s-r",
    "None of these",

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "sin 2B = 2Sin B is true B is equal to",
option:[
    "90 degree",
    "60 degree",
    "30 degree",
    "0 degree",

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "The Probability of getting a spade card from a well shffled deck of 52 cards is",
option:[
    "1/13",
    "1/4",
    "12/13",
    "3/4",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "If X and Y are compementary angles, then",
option:[
    "Sin X = sin Y",
    "Tan X = Tan Y",
    "Cos X = Cos Y",    
    "Sec X = Cosec Y",

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "One of the methods for determining mode is",
option:[
    "Mode=2 Median-3 Mean",
    "Mode=3 Median-2 Mean",
    "Mode=3 Mean-2 Median",
    "Mode=2 Mean-3 Median ",

],
answer:2, 
}]